LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vloskutov

Website: https://pogromist.io

Github: https://github.com/p0gr0mist

Summary

- Master of Science Degree in Computer Science and Engineering graduate has a strong foundation in the development of VLSI physical design tools, and in the development of CAD tools for digital IC and systems.
- Experienced in implementation modified algorithms for VLSI physical design automation steps, such as the placement and routing, and in optimizing software in C/C++.
- A responsible and reliable individual with a desire to grow professionally and learn new technology.

Skills Summary

Skill	Tool (if applicable)	Avg. experience (years)
Programming Languages	C/C++, Python, SQL, Java, Perl, Tcl/Tk, Bash, PowerShell	5
Frameworks and Tools	Django, Bootstrap, Elasticsearch, Celery	1
Algorithms	For standard cell placement and global routing	3
Databases	SQLite, PostgreSQL	3
Web	HTML, CSS, XML, JavaScript	8
Platforms	Windows/Unix/Linux	8
Miscellaneous	Mercurial, Git, Eclipse, MS Visual Studio	5
System Administration	LAN/WAN/NOC Administration, Technical Support	5

Education

National Research University of Electronic Technology, Moscow, Russia	September 2013 – June 2015
Master of Science Degree in Computer Science and Engineering	GPA: 3.93/4.00
National Research University of Electronic Technology, Moscow, Russia	September 2009 – July 2013
Bachelor of Science Degree in Electronics and microelectronics	GPA: 3.04/4.00

Professional Experience

Verifeed, LLC, Washington DC

September 2016 – December 2016

Software Engineering Intern

- Software development and maintenance that is oriented on social intelligence analytics using Django, Bootstrap.
- Tools development and maintenance for generating reports using Django, PostgreSQL, Git.
- Agile Development and Test Driven Development.

Company «Angstrem-Telecom», Moscow, Russia

September 2014 – May 2015

Junior Network Engineer

- Testing of embedded network devices (SoC RTL89xxC) based on OpenWrt and Octopus using Bash, iptables.
- Finding/Fixing bugs and maintaining code using C/C++, Git.
- Eperience with RTL8188{C|CU|CUS}, RT8192{C|CU} wifi chips, RS-232 interface, U-Boot bootloader.
- Debricked routers using JTAG, Serial console.
- Fixing web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Writing documentation for network equipment using MS Office.

Technical Specialist

- Support for local office network in working condition, setting of office software and equipment.
- Configuration and maintenance of servers based on Windows and *nix, and other network equipment.
- Experience of using RS-232, RS-485 communications (corresponding protocols) for debugging (via serial console), debrick and firmware replacement of network devices.
- Installation and maintenance of access control system Apollo (running APACS). Firnware replacement, configuration, and interaction of Apollo's controllers.
- Configuration and maintenance of software (asterisk) and hardware PBX.

Projects

Tetris algorithm April 2015 – May 2015

Implementation Tetris algorithm for legalization of standard cell placement.

Class: Algorithms for Analysis & Optimization of Very-Large-Scale Integration & Systems on a Chip.

Used: C/C++, STL, GLUT.

Kernighan-Lin algorithm

March 2015 – April 2015

Implementation Kernighan-Lin Algorithm for circuit partitioning.

Class: Algorithms for Analysis & Optimization of Very-Large-Scale Integration & Systems on a Chip. Used: C/C++, STL.

PlacerSA November 2014 – May 2015

Placer for standard cell placement (global & detailed) based on modified algorithm "simulated annealing" for VLSI and FPGA. Used: C/C++, STL, GLUT, Batch scripting.